this is the story of your enslavement
how it came to be and how you can
finally be free like all animals human
beings want to dominate and exploit the
resources around them at first we mostly
hunted and fished and ate off the land
but then something magical and terrible
happen to our minds we became alone
among the animals afraid of death and a
future loss and this was the start of a
great tragedy and an even greater
possibility you see when we become
afraid of death of injury and
imprisonment we become controllable and
so valuable in a way that no other
resource could ever be the greatest
resource for any human being to control
there's not natural resources or tools
or animals or land but other human
beings
you can frightened an animal because
animals are afraid of pain in the moment
but you cannot frighten an animal with a
loss of Liberty with torture or
imprisonment in the future because
animals have very little sense of
tomorrow you cannot threaten a cow with
torture or a sheep with debt you cannot
swing a sword at a tree and scream at it
to produce more fruit or hold a burning
torch to a field and demand more wheat
you cannot get more eggs by threatening
a hen but you can get a man to give you
his eggs by threatening him this human
fire
has been the most profitable and
destructive occupation throughout
history and it is now reaching its
destructive climax human society cannot
be rationally understood until it is
seen for what it is a series of farms
where human farmers own human livestock
some people get confused because
governments provide health care and
water and education and roads and thus
imagine that there is some benevolence
at work nothing could be further from
the reality farmers provide health care
in irrigation and training to their
livestock some people get confused
because we are allowed certain liberties
and that's imagine that our governments
protect our freedoms but farmers plant
their crops a certain distance apart to
increase their yields and will allow
certain animals larger stalls or fields
if it means they will produce more meat
and milk in your country your tax farm
your farmer grants you certain freedoms
not because he cares about your
liberties but because he wants to
increase his profits are you beginning
to see the nature of the cage you were
born into there have been four
or major phases of human farming the
first phase in ancient Egypt was direct
and brutal human compulsion human bodies
were controls but the creative
productivity of the human mind remained
beyond the reach of the whip and the
brand of the shackles slaves remained
woefully underproductive and required
enormous resources to control the second
phase was the Roman model wherein slaves
were granted some capacity for freedom
ingenuity and creativity which raised
their productivity this increased the
wealth of ROM and thus the tax income of
the Roman government and with this
additional wealth Rome became an empire
destroying the economic freedoms that
fed its power and collapsed I'm sure
that this does not seem entirely
unfamiliar after the collapse
from the feudal model introduced the
concept of livestock ownership and
Taxation instead of being directly owned
peasants farmed land that they could
retain as long as they paid off the
local warlords this model eventually
broke down due to the continual
subdivision of productive land and was
destroyed during the enclosure movement
when land was consolidated and hundreds
of thousands of peasants were kicked off
their ancestral lands because new
farming techniques made larger farms
more productive with fewer people the
increased productivity of the later
Middle Ages created the excess food
required for the expansion of towns and
cities which in turn gave rise to the
modern democratic model of human
ownership as displaced peasants flooded
into the cities a huge stock of cheap
human capital became available to the
rising industrialists and the ruling
class of human farmers quickly realized
that they could make more money by
letting their livestock choose their own
occupations under the Democratic model
direct slave ownership has been replaced
by the Mafia model the Mafia rarely owns
businesses directly but rather sends
thugs around once a month to steal from
the business owners you are now allowed
to choose your own occupation which
raises your productivity and thus the
taxes you can pay to your masters value
this time in your life kids because this
is the time of your life when you still
have your choices that goes by so fast
when you're a teenager I think you can
do anything and you do your twenties or
thirties you raise your family you make
a little money you think yourself what
have my twenties 40s you go a little
potbelly you grow another chin the music
starts to get too loud one of your old
girlfriends in high school becomes a
grandma 50 you have a minor surgery
you'll call it a procedure what is the
surgery six feet you'll have a major
surgery the music is still loud but it
doesn't matter but you can hear it
anyway 70s you and the wife retire to
Fort Lauderdale study ding dinner two
o'clock in the afternoon
if lunch around 10:00 breakfast the
night before then most of your time
wandering around malls looking for the
ultimate sort of yogurts and muttering
up on the kids don't call how come the
kids don't call the 80s you'll have a
major stroke end up battling some
Jamaica nurse your wife can't stand up
you call mama any questions your few
freedoms are preserved because they are
profitable to your owners the great
challenge of the Democratic model is
that increases in wealth and freedom
threaten the farmers the ruling class is
initially profit from a relatively free
market and capital and labor but as
their livestock become more used to
their freedoms and growing wealth they
begin to question why they need rulers
at all oh well nobody ever said that
human farming was easy keeping the tax
law
stuck securely in the compounds of the
ruling classes is a three-phase process
the first is to indoctrinate the young
through government quote education as
the wealth of democratic countries grew
government schools were universally
inflicted in order to control the
thoughts and souls of the livestock the
second phase is to turn citizens against
each other through the creation of
dependent livestock it is very difficult
to rule human beings directly through
force and where it can be achieved
it remains crippling the underproductive
as can be seen in North Korea human
beings do not breed well or produce
efficiently in direct captivity ah but
if human beings believe that they are
free then they will produce much more
for their farmers the best way to
maintain this illusion of freedom is to
put some of the livestock on the payroll
of the farmer those cows have become
dependent on the existing hierarchy will
then attack any other cows who point out
the violence hypocrisy and immorality of
human ownership
officers positioned grant face-first on
the floor with one officer near his head
a second near his back and a third
officer standing nearby there appeared
to be a brief struggle then a two year
veteran BART officer stands draws his
weapon and fires freedom is slavery and
slavery is freedom if you can get the
cows to attack each other whenever
anybody brings up the reality of their
situation then you don't have to spend
nearly as much controlling them directly
those cows who become dependent upon the
stolen largesse of the farmer will
violently oppose any questioning of the
virtue of human ownership and the
intellectual and artistic classes always
and forever dependent upon the farmers
will say to anyone who demands freedom
from ownership you will harm your fellow
cows the livestock are thus kept
enclosed by shifting the moral
responsibility for the destructiveness
of a violent system to those who demand
real freedom the third phase is to
continual external threats so that the
frightened livestock cling to the
protection of the farmers this system of
human farming is now nearing its end the
terrible tragedies of modern Western
economic systems have occurred not in
spite of but because of past economic
freedoms the massive increases in
Western wealth throughout the 19th
century resulted from economic freedoms
and it was this very increase in wealth
that fed the size and power of the state
whenever the livestock become
exponentially more productive you get a
corresponding increase in the number of
farmers and their dependents the growth
of the state is always proportional to
the preceeding economic freedoms
economic freedoms create wealth and the
wealth attracts more thieves and
political parasites whose greed then
destroys the economic freedoms in other
words freedom metastasizes the cancer of
the state the government that's
the smallest will always end up the
largest this is why there can be no
viable and sustainable alternative to a
truly free and peaceful society a
society without political rulers without
human ownership without the violence of
taxation and statism to be truly free
it's both very easy and very hard we
avoid the horror of our enslavement
because it is so painful to see it
directly we dance around the endless
violence of our dying system because we
fear the attacks of our fellow livestock
but we can only be kept in the cages we
refuse to see break up to see the farm
is to leave it